

JULIUS HSU
Full Stack Developer

CONTACT INFO

+1 647 236 6568

juliushsu07@gmail.com

juliushsu.com

in linkedin.com/in/juliushsu

github.com/juliushsu07

Toronto, ON, Canada

EDUCATION

2017 - 2018
Web Development
Lighthouse Labs Bootcamp

2010 - 2015

Computer Engineering University of British Columbia

LANGUAGES

English
Full professional proficiency

Mandarin Chinese Native proficiency

ABOUT ME

I'm a positive, enthusiastic and competent Full Stack Developer, seeking longterm employment with a company where I can immerse myself in their brand and ambitions!

During my last 4+ years working as a Software Engineer and a Senior Operation Specialist, I have gained a lot of experience in building web applications using ReactJS as the front-end and NodeJS and ExpressJS as the back-end with MongoDB. I enjoy taking on new challenges, and I learn new kits and frameworks in my free time to stay updated with current technology. I strive to write better code that meets first-class standards, and I desire to make an impact in the world of software development!

SKILLS

Programing Languages
Frameworks and libraries
System and database

JavaScript TypeScript Python HTML5 CSS3
ReactJS NodeJS ExpressJS Flask Boostrap
MongoDB SQL Firebase AWS Linix Git Docker

EXPERIENCE

Mar 2020 - Nov 2022 Cluep Inc.

Senior Ad Operation Specialist

Single-handily built a one-page Validation App using React, NodeJS and ExpressJS, which performed READ and UPDATE operations to MongoDB database. This app consisted of several validation tools and was used by ALL Operation team members to ensure everyday tasks were completed with a safety net.

Oversaw the integration of the Validation App with the company's admin dashboard. The integration was done with the Redux-observable middleware, bundling tools into one single checkpoint that performed validations on 10 components at once.

Trained and onboarded 10+ Operation team members over the course of 4+ years.

Managed a team of 3 interns who worked on machine-learning image annotations.

Feb 2018 - Mar 2020 Cluep Inc.

Junior Software Engineer

Created and maintained over 50 automation python scripts for the Operation team.

Designed and pitched bulk upload features for several front-end components of the admin dashboard. These features were later built and in turn increased operation efficiency by 95% for many everyday tasks.

Developed, maintained and performed Manual Test Plans for up to 40 components of the company's admin dashboard.

Jun 2016 - Sep 2016 Clever Banana Studios Inc.

Web Developer Intern

Developed and maintained code for in-house and client websites primarily using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.

Designed and recommended improvements to new and existing website templates.

Assisted in troubleshooting issues on client websites.

Worked closely with a small team consisting of 2 designers and 1 developer.